## Pung Kah Jyun | Mobile No.: +65 96254652 | Email: kahjyun@hotmail.com |

LinkedIn: Pung KahJyun | LinkedIn

## **Objective**

To be able to socialize by frequently working with, communicating with, and learning from systems/people. Solution-driven individual. Would enjoy utilizing my analytical and social skills in driving the attainment of business goals. Aspire to be a professional worker, to be involved in or be part of a management team; after working for several years in the industry. Seeking for any kind of challenges, as to broaden my job knowledge.

#### INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

# United Overseas Bank Thailand

**HR Student Intern** 

"Deployed to three HR functions (Talent & Dev/HRBP/Recruitment)"

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Analyse and find insights in Employees' Engagement Survey
- Suggest improvements to UOBT's Handbook
- Update headcount of various employees in different functions
- Designed communication plans
  - \*Letter of recommendation included\*

Nanyang Polytechnic Singapore

HR Student Intern

"Recruitment Agency" Feb 2019 – Jun 2019

- Planned Recruitment Drive for Nanyang Polytechnic
- Conduct Interviews with Potential Candidates
- Created On Job Training (OJT)
- Design and post Job Posters

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Grab Singapore Admin + Customer Service Apr 2020 – Jul 2020

Handled administrative duties such as data entries and updating into the system (Profile, Insurance checking)

- Customer services such as attending to drivers' queries and feedback
- Any other ad hoc admin & customer service duties

PartyMojo Pte Ltd Singapore

## **Part-Time Live Food Station Server**

Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

- Set up & Clean-up of Machines (Popcorn, Candy Floss, others)
- Served food at specific food stations during service times
- Helped guests with a cheerful disposition

#### **Education**

National University of Singapore

Degree in Information Systems (School of Computing)

Aug 2022 - Present

Nanyang Polytechnic Singapore

Diploma in Business Management (Human Resources + International Business)

Apr 2017 - May 2020

- CGPA: 3.78/4
- Director's List Academic Achievement Award recipient [4 out of 6 semesters]
- CCA: Executive Team Senior Member

## **Chung Cheng High (Yishun)**

Singapore

As in Maths and Science for N & O Levels

Jan 2010 - Dec 2016

- CCA: Running Club Chairman (2013 2015)
- CCA: Outdoor Activities Club Vice Chairman (2015 2016)

#### **Technical Expertise**

Proficient in Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, and Excel Familiar with Basic HTML, Python, Java, Tableau Possess good leadership, management, and verbal communication skills Bilingual – English & Mandarin

#### Certifications/Awards

Engineering Mathematics – Calculus	May 2022 - Aug 2022
Scientific Computing with Python (freeCodeCamp)	Feb 2022
https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/KahJyun/scientific-computing-with-python-v7	
Data Analytics Using Excel (Nanyang Polytechnic)	Mar 2022
Platoon Best Award (Sergeant Cadet School)	Nov 2020
Director's List Academic Achievement Award recipient [4 out of 6 semesters]	2017 – 2020
SBM Executive Team Recognition	2017 – 2019
Participation in Industry Digitalisation Masterclass	2017
MOE Scholarships Award	2012
MOE Good Progress Award	2011 & 2015

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

#### Volunteering

#### **Foochow Methodist Church Missionary Trip to Indonesia Volunteer Leader**

Indonesia

Dec 2019

- In charge of organizing games and camp activities for 30 children to encourage interaction with one another.
- Communicated with Indonesians with different cultures and lifestyles and develop multicultural sensitivity and appreciation of diverse cultures.

#### **Singapore Salvation Army Assembling Staff**

**Singapore** 

2020

- Allocated unused and used appliances to their respective locations
- Coordinated with permanent staff on procedures to be followed in the collection, distribution, and filling/retrieving of the items

#### Coding

GitHub: Fastumkj's gists (github.com)

**Anime** 

**Mobile Games** 

Learning new languages